<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on </title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Judy Kay</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I lead the multi-disciplinary Human Centred Technology Research Cluster at the University of Sydney, Australia.
My research is in the areas of Artificial Intelligence in Education (AIED), Ubiquitous Computing (Ubicomp) and Human Computer Interaction (HCI). A core focus of my work has been to create system that enable people to harness their personal data for lifelong and lide-wide learning. This means creating systems and interfaces that for user models so thay people can scrutinize their model and its use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected recent Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Publication List</title>
      <link>/home/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/pubs/</guid>
      <description>For a full list of my publications, see Google scholar and dblp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent News Posts</title>
      <link>/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/posts/</guid>
      <description>14-18 Jun, 2021, Invited keynote at the 2021 conference on Artificial Intelligence in Education, AIED 2021, Utrecht/Virtual, Netherlands, Theme: Mind the Gap: AIED for Equity and Inclusion.
 14-19 Mar, 2021, Invited keynote at ACM SIGIR Conference on Human Information Interaction and Retrieval (CHIIR’21)
 8-9 Feb, 2021, Invited speaker at BIOTech Futures Challenge Virtual Symposium for high school students, Topic: Human-centred AI for human health
 10-11 Dec, 2020: Closing Keynote at Empowering Learners for the AI Age, Title: Empowering People to Harness their Data for Lifelong and Life-wide Learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/projects/</guid>
      <description>My current projects are:
 Lifelong and lifewide user modelling: creating interfaces and infrastructure for people to control and harness their personal long term data for their learning.
 Dashboards for long term personal data.
 Tackling truth decay by creating personalised interfaces that enable people make judge the trustworthiness of online science news.
 E-textbook of the future.
 Ambient appliances and personal sensors to help people tackle long term personal goals for health and wellness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editorial and Research Leadership</title>
      <link>/home/editorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/editorial/</guid>
      <description>Editor-in-chief (2012 -) IJAIED: International Journal of Artificial Intelligence in Education | Springer site | IAIED | Submissions and reviews | ERIC | May 2020 Citescore 9.1, rank 9&amp;frasl;1254 Education, 7&amp;frasl;128 Computational Theory and Maths
 Editor (2018-2020) Interactive, Mobile, Wearable and Ubiquitous Technologies (IMWUT) | PCS submissions
 Editorial Board (2000 - ): User Modeling and User-Adapted Interaction: The Journal of Personalization Research (UMUAI) | submissions | SCImago HCI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>My current teaching at at University of Sydney:
 DATA3506 - Human-in-the-loop data analytics | Syllabus
 COMP5427 - Usability Engineering | Syllabus
  Resources from previous teaching:
 Problem Based Learning (PBL) for First Year Programming. Over several years, we refined this valuable way to teach first programming with a very broad problem-based perspective. We trialled the approach and compared matched populations. If you are considering this approach you may find the resources below useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>/home/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/students/</guid>
      <description>Current research students:
 Alan Yung - Exploring support for oncologists with the data that drives decisions in diagnosis and treatments (Co-supervisor: Tim Shaw)
 Bernard Bucalon - Visualising Performance Data (Co-supervisors: Tim Shaw, Kerri Brown)
 Josh Burridge - The Investigation and Development of Non-Traditional Laboratories in Science and Engineering Education (Co-supervisors: David Lowe , Keith Willey)
 Ying An Chen - Evaluation of Benefits Using a Third-Person in Virtual Reality Educational Games (Co-supervisors: Marcus Carter, Soojeong Yoo)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Conferences</title>
      <link>/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/talks/</guid>
      <description> ACE 2021 Conf 1-5 Feb, 2021 SIGCSE Conf 13-20 Mar, 2021 ito appear: (A Data-centric Computing Curriculum for a Data Science Major, Fekete, Kay, Röhm) AIED 2021 Paper deadline: 1 Feb 2021 Abstracts, 8 Feb papers, 1 Mar workshops, Conf 14-18 June, 2021 LAK 2021 Deadlines: Conf April 12-16, 2021 (Early rego 25 Feb) IUI 2021 Conf 13-17 April, 2021 Ubicomp 2021 Ubicomp 2022 in Australia  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>